<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Safa Pekhawar</string>

    <string name="sp">SHARED_PREF</string>
    <string name="spUID">USER_ID</string>
    <string name="spUName">USER_NAME</string>
    <string name="spUEmail">USER_EMAIL</string>
    <string name="spUMobile">USER_MOBILE</string>
    <string name="spUPic">PROFILE_PIC</string>
    <string name="spUC">UNION_COUNCIL</string>
    <string name="spNC">NEIGHBOURHOOD_COUNCIL</string>

    <string name="title_activity_drawer">DrawerActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="call_center">1334 کو کال ملایں | Call 1334</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="str_safa_pekhawar_eng">
        Safa Pekhawar
        \nPeshawar produces around 700 tons of municiple waste every day which is increasing day by day
        with the rate of 3KG/day. Around 50% of the municiple waste remains on the place where it is produced.
        It makes the surrounding air hazardious for living.
        \n
        \nSafa Pekhawar is a community engagement app through which people complaint about the water &amp;
        sanitation related issues in their neighbourhood.
        \n
        \nThrough this app people take picture of the garbage, damaged water drainage system or any other
        issue related to water &amp; sanitation in Peshawar and send it to WSSP Complaint Cell.
        \n
        \nAfter receiving the complaint, WSSP admin team notifies the cleaning team about the location of issue.
        WSSP Cleaning team reaches the destination and resolves the issue.

    </string>
    <string name="str_safa_pekhawar_urdu">
        صفا پیبنور
        \n
پشاور تقریبا 700 ٹن میونسپل گندگی روزانہ پیدا کرتا ہے جس میں 3 کلو گندگی کا اضافہ روزانہ کےحساب سے ہورہا ہے. تقریبا 50% گندگی اسی جگاپڑھی رہتی ہے جہاں پیدا  ہوتی  ہے جو کہ اپنے ارد گرد ماحول کوجینے کے لئے  خطرناک بنادیتی ہے
        \n\n
        صفا پیبنور ہمارے معاشرے کے لوگوں کے اینگیجمنٹ کے لئے بنایا گیاایسا ایپلیکیشن ہے جس کے ذریعے لوگ  پانی اور صفائی سے متعلقہ اپنے
پڑوس کے مسائل کے بارے میں شکایت جمع کر سکتے ہیں
        \n\n
        اس ایپلیکیشن کے ذریعے لوگ کوڑا کرکٹ، گندگی،بند نالی اور صفائی سے متعلقہ مسائل کے بارے میں
        ڈبلیو ایس ایس پی کمپلینٹ سیل کے پاس آسانی سے شکایت جمع کر سکتے ہیں
        \n\n
شکایت موصولہونے کے بعد ڈبلیو ایس ایس پی کمپلینٹ  سیل ٹیم صفائی کےعملے کو مطلع کرتی ہے جو کہ مسلہ کی جگا پہنچ کر مسلہ حل کرتی ہے.

    </string>

    <string name="how_to_urdu">
        سٹیپ 1
        \n
ایپلیکیشن کھولیں
\n\n
سٹیپ 2
        \n
مختلف شکایات کے اقسام کے لئے انگلیوں کو دائیں اور بائیں سکرول کریں
\n\n
سٹیپ 3
        \n
اپنے مطلوبہ شکایت کی قسم کو منتخب کریں
\n\n
سٹیپ 4
        \n
متعلقہ مسلے کی تصویر لیں
\n\n
سٹیپ 5
        \n
متعلقہ مسلہ جس گلی میں ہے اس کا پتا لکھنے کے لیے  “گلی کا پتا لکھیں” بٹن دبائیں
\n\n
سٹیپ 6
        \n
 شکایت درج کرنے کے لئے  “ درج کریں ” دبائیں. آپ کی شکایت جمع ہو جائیگی
آپ شکایت کے  بارے  میں  جاننے  کے لئے  مینو  میں  جائیں  اور  “ میرے شکایات” کا بٹن دبائیں
آپ 1334 کودراکٹ کالکر کہ بھی شکایت  کے بارے میں  جان  سکتے ہیں


    </string>


    <string name="how_to_eng">Step 1:
        \nOpen the application and Sign In.
        \n
        \nStep 2:
        \nScroll between the complaint types by swiping fingers left and right.
        \n
        \n
        Step 3:
        \nSelect the complaint type you wish to move with.
        \n
        \nStep 4:
        \nTake picture of the related issue/problem you are facing.
        \n
        \nStep 5:
        \nClick “Add Street Address” button. In the next screen, type the street address in which the
        issue/problem presists.
        \n
        \nStep 6:
        \nClick “Submit” and your complaitn will be
        submitted and you will be provided a complaint number. You can check status of your
        complaint in the “My Complaints” option in the
        sliding bar. You can also check status of your
        complaint through a direct call to 1334 by
        providing the complaint number you are given.
    </string>

    <string name="thank_you_eng">Thank you\n
        Your complaint has been submitted.\n
        #C_NO# is your complaint number.
    </string>
    <string name="thank_you_urdu">
        شکریہ\n
        آپ کی شکایت درج کی جاچکی ہے\n
        #C_NO# آپ کا شکایت نمبر ہے
    </string>

    <string name="feedback_eng">Your complaint number #C_NO# has been resolved.
        \n
        Are you satisfied with the results?
    </string>
    <string name="feedback_urdu">آپ کی شکایات نمبر #C_NO# حل کی جاچکی ہے
        \n
        کیا آپ نتائج سے مطمئن ہیں؟
    </string>
</resources>


